&gt；&gt；扬声器1：这叫做布局抖动。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: It's
called layout thrashing.
真正的术语是强制同步布局。
The real term is forced
synchronous layout.
我们称它为布局颠簸，因为让我们看看真的很酷。
We're gonna call it layout thrashing,
because let's see really cool.
让我们实话实说，就像当你有一件事叫做布局颠覆和
Let's be really honest like when you have
one thing called layout thrashing and
另一个称为强制同步布局，
another one called forced
synchronous layout,
你每次都选择布局颠簸。
you choose layout thrashing every time.
因此，您可以执行一系列操作，导致浏览器停止并计算
So there's a set of things you can do that
cause the browser to stop and calculate
风格和布局，就像我们看到的一样，询问它就是其中之一。
style, and layout, and as we saw like
asking about it is one of those things.
这是我的应用程序中的一些代码，我只是从字面上
This is some code from my
application where I just literally
在编辑器中做了第一件可能的事，
did the first possible
thing in the editor,
我们有一个按钮模块，就像呼吁行动按钮一样。
which we have a button module
like the call to action button.
然后我点击了一个录音，我把它拖了进来，我停止了录音。
And I hit a recording, I dragged it in and
I stopped the recording.
因为我的整个计划就是喜欢踢来踢去，他们有很多可以找到的例子
Cuz my whole plan was to like kick around,
they have a lot to find an example and
一个现实世界的应用程序向你展示。
a real world application to show you.
结果，这真的是我做的第一件事。
Turned out, it was literally
the first thing that I did.
你可以看到，就像Chrome可以检测到它一样，
You can see that like if
Chrome can detect it,
它会在上面放一个红色的小三角形。
it will put a little
red triangle up there.
就像是告诉你，嘿，
And like basically tell you, hey,
第四次回流可能是瓶颈的表现。
a fourth reflow is a likely
performance of bottle neck.
就像是我抓到你这么做。
It's like I caught you doing this.
我觉得你应该知道
I think you should know about it and
你可以看到所有这些东西都在适当的地方。
you can kind of like see
all of that stuff in place.
因此，即使在大型应用程序中，它们也是我的第一件事
So like even in a large application like
they was literally the first thing that I
我试过了，但我并不是去寻找一个异教徒的流动。
tried, it wasn't like I went looking for
a pagery flow.
我确实去寻找了一个异教徒的流动。
I did go looking for a pagery flow.
它立即找到了它，节省了我一大堆工作[笑]，但是
It saved me a bunch of work [LAUGH]
by finding it immediately, but
谈论这件事对我的道德权威没有帮助。
it didn't help my moral
authority talking about this.
但这是我在那里发现的第一件事。
But it was the very first
thing that I found in there.
所以其中一种定义，
So one of the kind of definitions,
布局颠簸发生在JavaScript剧烈的时候，这就是为什么我选择了这句话。
layout thrashing occurs when JavaScript
violently, that's why I picked this quote.
写入，然后多次从DOM读取，导致文档回流。
Writes, then reads from the DOM multiple
times, causing document reflows.
所以，是的，每次我们阅读的时候，我们都必须弄清楚所有东西的大小。
So yeah, every time we read like we have
to figure out the size of everything.
然后一旦它获得最新的信息，也许只读一次。
And then once it gets the most up to date
information, maybe just reads it once.
酷，没什么大不了的。
Cool, no big deal.
问题是浏览器很聪明，你想那是什么问题？
The problem is the browser is smart,
you're like what kind of problem is that?
如果你改变了一堆东西，
If you change a bunch of stuff,
浏览器有点像，记得我们说过，像移动操作是很好的。
the browser kind of like remember we
said like budging manipulation was good.
浏览器也有效地试图做到这一点。
The browsers effectively
trying to do that, as well.
你可以改变一大堆员工。
You can change a whole bunch of staff.
像我这样的浏览器直到像这样的每16毫秒才会生成新的帧
The browsers like I don't make new frames
until like every 16 milliseconds like
让他们拥有吧。
let them have that it.
当我准备画下一幅画的时候，我会忘记什么变化，
When I'm getting ready to draw the next
frame, I'm gonna forgot what change,
然后我转发页面。
then I relayout the page.
你这里的问题是我们改变了一些东西。
The problem that you have
here is we changed something.
我们测量它，我们改变一些东西，我们测量它。
And we measure it,
we change something and we measure it.
就像浏览器不知道，它想要得到你，
Like the browser doesn't know,
it wants to get you,
它不想给出那个酒吧的宽度。
it doesn't want to give what
the width was of that bar.
上次渲染时，你改变了一些东西。
Last time it rendered,
you changed something.
它想给你提供最新的信息，
It wants to get you the most
up to date information,
因为那个盒子可能不在你想的地方了。
cuz that box might not be
where you think it is anymore.
所以每次你测量的时候，如果你上次测量的时候有什么变化，
So every time you measure, if anything has
changed from the last time you measured,
浏览器必须经过并且想要了解世界的新状态。
the browser has to go through and like
figure out the new state of the world.
当然，这不是很好吗？
Sure, is that not great?
显然，但问题出在哪里是在一个循环中。
Obviously, but
where it became a problem was in a loop.
我们检查了，我们改变了。
We checked, we changed.
这导致我们重新计算样式布局，重新计算样式布局。
Which caused we recalculate style lay out,
recalculate style lay out.
每当你看到其中的模式，就像有时你在迭代和
Whenever you kind of see that pattern in
there like sometimes you are iterating and
这很自然，但你看到他就像一个长长的街区在那里。
it's natural, but you saw that for
h was like one long block in there.
当你看到这些模式，你注意到你吹过了16毫秒
When you see those patterns and you notice
you're blowing through the 16 milliseconds
对于一个框架，你有一个问题。
for a frame, you have a problem.
如果Chrome Like在这种情况下给了你一个红色的小东西，
And if Chrome like goes as far as to give
you the little red thing in that case,
你真的知道你有问题
you truly know you have a problem and
这是首先要寻找的东西之一。
this is kind of one of
the first things to look for.
所以，是的，浏览器基本上是想弄清楚它是否需要进行新的更新
So yeah, the browser basically wants to
figure out if it has to get new updated
每次更改后的布局信息。
layout information after every
time you change something.
你问它东西，它不知道。
You asked it for stuff, it didn't know.
它试图弄清楚。
It tried to figure it out.
所以它停止了，它回流了页面，给你提供了信息。
So it stopped, it reflowed the page and
got you the information.
那我们怎么解决这个问题？
So how do we solve this?
嗯，我们之前在代码中看到了一个解决方案。
Well, we saw a solution
in the code before.
如果你把所有的阅读和写作分开，
If you separate all the reading
from all the writing,
你应该像读很多遍一样好。
you should be good like
read a bunch of times.
不要更改页面，获取所需的所有信息，然后继续
Don't change the page, get all of the
information you need, then go ahead and
更改页面。
do the page changes.
所以就像循环中的第一个代码会触发布局脱粒。
So like the first code in a loop
would've triggered layout threshing.
第二个，我们读了一堆
The second one, we read a bunch and
然后我们根据这些信息写一堆这样的东西。
then we write a bunch like
based on that information.
它将为我们表演。
It is going to be performing for us.